vectormagic.com 2019-09-03

# Easily Convert Bitmaps To Vectors - Vector Magic

Effective Date: May 25, 2018. 

##  VectorMagic.com and Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. 

VectorMagic.com is owned and operated by Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. 

This policy applies to VectorMagic.com. Other web sites and services owned and operated by Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. have their own privacy policies. 

## Introduction

Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the [vectormagic.com](https://vectormagic.com/) website, and any other linked pages, features, content, or application services offered from time to time by Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. in connection therewith (collectively, the 'Website' or 'Service'), or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

## Information Collection and Use

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service. While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Additionally, we may collect other data that, while not itself personally identifiable, is associated in our systems with personally identifiable data. The listing below outlines the data that we collect, why we collect it, our legal basis under the General Data Protection Regulation for doing so, and our retention policies for each type of data. 

Accounts

Description
     To make purchases on VectorMagic.com, we require you to sign up for an account by providing us with your email address and a password (account credentials). We additionally record your IP address and the date and time of account creation. 
Business Purpose
     Your account is our central record of your activity and purchases on VectorMagic.com. Your email address is how we identify you and your password is how we authenticate you. Your email address is also used to communicate with you, as described further below in our Email Policy. Your IP address is used for credit card and account fraud prevention, and customer support. The date and time you signed up is used for customer support. 
Legal Basis
     We need these records in order to perform services on your behalf, and we are legally required to maintain records of purchases. 
Retention
     Account credentials are generally retained indefinitely for the convenience of the user. 
Image Processing Records

Description
     We offer image processing services. In the course of using these services, you upload images to us, which we store and process on your behalf. In addition to storing the image itself, we also record a variety of associated information, such as meta-data, configuration settings, and image processing output. 
Business Purpose
     These image processing records are the main deliverable that you get from using our service. We retain them on your behalf so that you can view and download them as you wish, and to provide customer support. From time to time, we may also use them to improve the image processing algorithms that underlie the services we offer. 
Legal Basis
     We need these records in order to perform services on your behalf. 
Retention
     Records not associated with an account are deleted or anonymized within a year of creation. Image processing records associated with an account are retained indefinitely. 
Purchase Records

Description
     When you make a purchase on VectorMagic.com, we collect: 

Payment Method
     When you provide us with your payment method, we may collect data associated with it such as any reference email address, the type of card, the name on the card, the last four digits of the card number, the expiration date, and any reference addresses. 
Subscription Details
     We may offer a subscription that allows the customer to access the services offered on VectorMagic.com. When you subscribe, we record relevant subscription details such as the date and time, the subscription plan you selected, and your current IP address. If you later elect to change plans or cancel, we record a log of actions taken, including the date and time and your current IP address. 
Transaction
     Each payment you make to us is recorded. We record relevant transaction details such as the date and time, the amount, the payment method used, and your IP address (when available). 
Business Purpose
     Purchases are central to how we earn money and how you gain access to the services we offer. Purchase records are essential for financial accounting, legal compliance, strategic planning, and general operations. IP addresses and timestamps are used for fraud prevention and customer support. 
Legal Basis
     We need it in order to perform services on your behalf, and we are legally required to maintain records of purchases. 
Retention
     All purchase-related records are retained for the legally required period and then anonymized. 
Cookies

Description
     Cookies are data stored by your browser on your device at the direction of a website, and provided to the website with each web request. Further details on cookies and our use of them are provided in a dedicated Cookies Policy below. 
Business Purpose
     We use cookies to identify you and your preferences so that we can perform services on your behalf. We collect web analytics to track Website performance, improve our services, and related business purposes. 
Legal Basis
     We need them in order to perform services on your behalf, and in order to develop and improve our Service. 
Retention
     Cookies are stored in your browser and can be deleted by you at any time. 
Email Communications

Description
     We use third-party email service providers to send, receive, and retain emails. Please see our Service Providers section below for further details. 

Transactional Emails
     We send transactional emails when you take certain actions on our Website such as making a purchase or signing up for a subscription, or when certain events occur, such as a renewal reminder or payment failure. We retain a copy of those emails on our email servers. 
Customer Support
     We offer customer support. Users may email us directly, or fill out a customer support form on our Website. Emails are retained by our email servers. Communication that is initiated through the customer support form is sent by our web servers to our email servers as an email. In addition to the information provided directly by the user in the form, we also collect information about the operating system and web browser they are using (collectively referred to as the 'user agent'). 

Business Purpose
     We retain transactional emails for disaster recovery, legal compliance, and accounting purposes. Retaining customer support communication is integral to providing the support. 
Legal Basis
     We need it in order to perform services on your behalf. 
Retention
     As with other purchase-related records, we retain transactional emails for the legally required time period and then delete them. Customer support emails are retained for the same period that the law requires us to retain transaction records. 

Unless otherwise noted, all records will be anonymized upon request when legally permissible. 

## Transfer of Data

Your information, including personal data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those in your jurisdiction. 

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

## Disclosure of Data

### Disclosure to Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. may be required to disclose your personal data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency). 

### Legal Requirements

Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. may disclose your personal data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary: 

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. 
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

## Security

The security of your data is important to us and we use industry standard technical and organizational measures to protect your information. For example, our Website is served over HTTPS and we implement data security organizational access controls. 

However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is completely and entirely secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially reasonable means to protect your data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

## Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), the European Union has declared that you have certain data protection rights: 

The rights to access, update or to delete the information we have on you
     Whenever made possible, you can access, update or request deletion of your personal data directly on our Website. If you are unable to perform these actions yourself, please contact us to assist you. 
The right of rectification
    You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete. 
The right to object
    You have the right to object to our processing of your personal data. 
The right of restriction
    You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information. 
The right to data portability
    You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format. 
The right to withdraw consent
     You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. relied on your consent to process your personal information. 
The right to complain
     You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your personal data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA). 

You can exercise all the aforementioned rights by emailing us at privacy@vectormagic.com. We shall address your request within 30 days of its receipt unless it is too complicated or we are dealing simultaneously with too many such requests. In the latter case, it may take us up to two additional months to address your request, but we will let you know if that is the case within 30 days of the receipt of your initial request. 

## Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ('Service Providers'), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used. The list below details some of the more significant third-party service providers that we employ: 

Email Services
     We may use third-party Service Providers to send, receive, or retain emails. 

G Suite
     We use Google's G Suite email service to send, receive and retain emails. 
Amazon Web Services
     We use Amazon Web Services Simple Email Service to send emails. 
Analytics
     We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service. 

Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data may be shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. 

You can opt-out of having your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity. 

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ 

Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing. 

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information. 

The payment processors we work with are: 

Stripe
     Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at: https://stripe.com/us/privacy 
PayPal or Braintree
     Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at: https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full 
Miscellaneous
     We may from time to time rely on various third parties to serve additional or enhanced content, such as embedded maps, reCAPTCHA, videos, user comments platform, customer support chat app, customer support platform, user forums, blogging platform, among others. Those services may place cookies and will have their own privacy policies. 

## 'Do Not Track' Signals

We do not support Do Not Track ('DNT'). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. 

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser. 

## Children's Privacy

Our Service is not directed to anyone under the age of 18 ('Children'). 

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Child has provided us with personal data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected personal data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. 

## Email Policy

We may use your personal data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us. 

## Cookies Policy

Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. uses cookies on the VectorMagic.com website. By using the Service, you consent to the use of cookies. 

Our Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how we use cookies, how third-parties we may partner with may use cookies on the Service, your choices regarding cookies and further information about cookies. 

### What are cookies

Cookies are small pieces of text sent to your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Service or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Service more useful to you. 

Cookies can be 'persistent' or 'session' cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your personal computer or mobile device when you go offline, while session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your web browser. 

###  How Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc. uses cookies 

When you use and access the Service, we may place a number of cookies files in your web browser. 

We use cookies for the following purposes: 

  * To enable certain functions of the Service 
  * For security purposes 
  * To provide analytics 
  * To store your preferences 

We use both session and persistent cookies on the Service and we use different types of cookies to run the Service: 

Essential cookies 
     We may use cookies to remember information that changes the way the Service behaves or looks, such as a user's language preference on the Service. 
Accounts-related cookies 
     We may use accounts-related cookies to authenticate users and prevent fraudulent use of user accounts. We may use these cookies to remember information that changes the way the Service behaves or looks, such as the 'remember me' functionality. 
Security cookies
    We use Security Cookies for security purposes. 
Third-party cookies

In addition to our own cookies, we may also use various third-parties cookies: 

Analytics cookies 
     We may use analytics cookies to track information how the Service is used so that we can make improvements. We may also use analytics cookies to test new advertisements, pages, features or new functionality of the Service to see how our users react to them. 
Payments cookies 
     These type of cookies may be used by payment processors for anti-fraud and related security measures. 
Miscellaneous cookies
     The miscellaneous third-party service providers that we may from time to time employ, may place additional third party cookies for various purposes. 

### What are your choices regarding cookies

If you'd like to delete cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser. 

Please note, however, that if you delete cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly. 

### Where can you find more information about cookies

You can learn more about cookies and the following third-party websites: 

  * AllAboutCookies: http://www.allaboutcookies.org/ 
  * Network Advertising Initiative: http://www.networkadvertising.org/ 

## Links to Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. 

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. 

## Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make a change to this privacy policy that we believe materially reduces your rights, we will notify you by email and/or by posting a notice on our Website. 

We will let you know via email and/or a notice on our Website, prior to the change becoming effective and update the 'effective date' at the top of this Privacy Policy. 

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. 

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Website, please send us a detailed message to privacy@vectormagic.com. 

Our postal address is: 

Cedar Lake Ventures, Inc.   
2500 Shadywood Rd Ste 510   
Excelsior, MN 55331-6203   
United States
